My daughter is not sponsored by Crazy
Art, but I bet she wishes she were
because she's obsessed with this Minnie
Mouse little kit, whatever. But I just
wanted to give them a shout-out. Um, the
Crazy Art Softy Dough is so much better
than Play-Doh. Do you want it back?
Sorry. She asked for that one back.
Sorry about that. Um, but like this was
a given to us by my sister. Um, do you
want this one also? I can't even talk
about it? Anyway, the moral of the story
is the Softy Dough is so much easier to
A, clean up than Play-Doh because it
doesn't crumble. Um, and
it's beautiful, honey. And B, it's
easier to keep the colors separated.
Play-Doh?
Yeah, that was crazy, right? Let's not
do that again, okay?
Okay. Anyway, shout-out to Crazy Art for
always making great stuff. Thank you,
Crazy Art.
Oh, she wants you to know that it came
with a fork also. Should we show them
the fork?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, hold on. Okay, she doesn't want to
give it to me. She wants you to see it,
but she can't be on camera, so it's not
going to happen. Anyway, this kit is
great. So, thanks.